Finding Aid for Robert D. Aldrich Collection
Bentley Historical Library
- Visual Materials
  - Photographs
    - Concord Spring Floods, circa 1910 (Box 14)
    - Concord Union Sunday School Picnic, 1912 (Box 14)
    - Concord Views
      - Business area (other than Main Street) (Box 14)
      - General and aerial views (Box 14)
      - Main Street (Box 14)
      - Residential (Box 14)
      - Booklet, 1912 (Box 14)
      - Slides, 1976-1980 (Box 14)
    - Cory family (Box 15)
      (includes photos of home in Coldwater, June W. Cory as a musician, Chicago College of Law Class of 1895 and tintype)
    - Couden, William-includes portrait in World War I chaplain's uniform (Box 15)
    - Cutter, Andrew H.-tintypes of home (Box 15)
    - D (various); includes Dewey family; Dodes family-includes photo of log cabin, Swains Lake; Dodge family-includes photos of homes (Box 15)
    - Eppler, Louis (Box 15)
    - Farmers Club (Box 15)
    - Fire, Bank Block, 1899-includes photo of steam fire engine (Box 15)
    - Flossdorf family-photo of home (Box 15)
    - F (various) (Box 15)
      (includes Frederick, Gordon - photo of children herding sheep in town; French, Delia, John, and Louise - includes photo of home, Spring Arbor, and tintype)
    - Fritz, La Vata (Box 15)
      (includes photos of threshing and portable sawmill)
    - Funeral displays (Box 15)
    - G.A.R., 1890s-photo with band (Box 15)
    - Ganiard family; Gaylord family (Box 15)
    - Gibbs, William L. (Box 15)
      (includes photo of drummers, 36th Indiana Volunteers, during Civil War)
    - Gillespey family (Box 15)
      (photo of home, Concord Township)
    - Goodrich family-includes photos of home, Concord (Box 15)
    - Goodwin family-includes photos of home (Box 15)
    - Grass Lake-photos of road construction (Box 15)
    - Groger family-includes photos of home (Box 15)
    - Groups, Miscellaneous (Box 15)
      (includes photos of Concord American Legion group and "womanless wedding")
    - Groups, Unidentified (Box 15)
    - Grover family (Box 15)
      (includes photo showing photographer in mirror)
    - H (various) folder 1 (Box 15)
      (includes Hadley family; Hall family; Hamblin family; Haviland, Delos W. and Fanny Wixom; Halstead family)
    - H (various) folder 2 (Box 15)
      (includes Hodge, Hiram C.; Hunsicker, Sam, Martha, and Clara-photo of home, Spring Arbor Township)
    - Horse riding, 1977 (Box 15)
    - Houses, Unidentified, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Hubbard, Dorothy, Album (Box 15)
      (includes photos of hunting scenes)
    - Hubbard family (Box 15)
      (includes photos of homes, high school [?] graduates 1888, children with toys, farm wagon, horse-drawn plow, and group with banjo player)
    - Hungerford family (Box 15)
    - Individuals, Unidentified, 2 folders (Box 15)
      (includes photos of soldier, 1890s and tintypes)
    - Jackson, George Kellicut (Box 15)
    - Jackson County Historical Society (unidentified photos) (Box 15)
    - Jackson High School Class of, 1910 (Box 15)
    - Keeler family-includes photos of home (Box 15)
    - Kellicut, Daniel Alanson (Box 15)
    - Krebill, Granger, Album (Box 15)
    - Krebill, Sally-includes photos of homes, Concord (Box 15)
    - Lamb Knitting Company, Colon (Box 15)
      (includes group portraits of workers)
    - L (various) (Box 15)
      (includes Lark, Lulu; Lamb, Rev. Isaac Wixom; Leonard, Clyde, photo in National Guard [?] uniform 1890s?)
    - Lumbering (Box 15)
    - Maccabees (Box 15)
    - McGee family-includes photo of home and tintype (Box 15)
    - McKenzie family (Box 15)
      (includes photos of girls dressed as dancers and hunting camp)
    - Malcolm family (Box 15)
      (includes photos of George Malcolm as youth and as judge in Philippines, photo of fire at Malcolm home, portrait of Charles E. Townsend, and tintype)
    - Mann family-includes photos of farm home (Box 16)
    - Mason, Almon Wood and Arthur (Box 16)
    - Michigan Central Railroad-includes photos and tintype of Concord railroad station (Box 16)
    - Millen, Dorothy-photo of child's birthday party (Box 16)
    - Mills
      - Concord Grist Mill (also known as Concord Roller Mill) (Box 16)
      - Soybean Mill, Concord (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 16)
      (includes photo of peace float in parade, ox cart, and unidentified wagon)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 16)
      (oversize folder UAm; includes photos of Warriner family, cart, carriage, Thom home, Concord aerial view)
    - Olmstead family (Box 16)
      (includes tintypes)
    - Opera House, Concord (Box 16)
    - Paddock family (Box 16)
      (includes photos of home)
    - P (various) folder 1 (Box 16)
      (includes Parlioman family; Parmalee, Milton; Parmeter family-includes photos of home and farm)
    - Picnic, 1940s (Box 16)
      (includes photos of tug-of-war, softball, and children's games)
    - P (various) folder 2 (Box 16)
      (includes Pierce, Blanche Lyman; Piper, William J. - includes tintype of unidentified Civil War soldier; Pomeroy, Austin-includes photos of home)
    - Pulaski, Mich (Box 16)
    - Quick family (Box 16)
    - Ray, Mark L. (Box 16)
    - Recreation, 1890s (Box 16)
      (includes photos of canoeing, outdoor checkers, and cottages at Colon and Swains Lake)
    - Republicans-visit of Homer Ferguson (Box 16)
    - Reynolds, Albert, family (Box 16)
      (wife Mary, daughter Hattie Reynolds Parsons)
    - Reynolds, Minnie (later Minnie Reynolds Olmstead), 2 envelopes (Box 16)
    - Reynolds families; include Reynolds, William H., family (wife Jennie); Reynolds, William L. M., family (wife Rachael Taylor) (Box 16)
      (includes photo of W.L.M. Reynolds, Jr. in Civil War uniform)
    - Rhodes family (Box 16)
    - Ri Dout family; Rollins family [tintype] (Box 16)
    - Rivers and lakes, Miscellaneous (Box 16)
      (includes photos of Kalamazoo River and Swains Lake)
    - Root family-includes photo of home and tintype (Box 16)
    - Rowley family-includes photo of home, Mussey Township (Box 16)
    - R (various); includes Rowlison, Gerald, family; Rutz family (Box 16)
    - "Sault Ste. Marie" Album, 1924-1926 (Box 16)
      (includes photos of unidentified family vacation in northern Michigan)
    - Schultz family-includes photo of home (Box 16)
    - S (various) folder 1 (Box 16)
      (includes Seymour, Franklin B.-includes photo of home; Simons, Homer and Carrie - includes photos of girls pulling taffy and Citizens' Military Training Corps members at Camp Custer)
    - Smalley family (Box 16)
      (includes tintypes and photo of fishing camp, Colon)
    - Smith, Chauncey and Nathaniel (Box 16)
    - Spratt/Sprats family, 2 envelopes (Box 16)
      (includes tintypes and photos of home, Spring Arbor, after fire)
    - Spring Arbor train wreck, 1914 (Box 16)
    - Stahley family (Box 16)
      (includes photos of home and tintypes, one of George A. Stahley in Masonic costume)
    - S (various) folder 1 (Box 16)
      (includes Stanley family; Stewart family - includes tintype; Stoddard family-includes photos of home)
    - Taylor and Todd families
      - Portraits (Box 16)
      - Houses (Box 16)
        (includes photos of tornado damage (1896), photos of house supposed to be stop on underground railroad, and tintypes and photos of farms)
    - Townsend family (Box 16)
    - Tucker family-photo of home (Box 16)
    - Van Scoter family (Box 16)
    - Waldo family-includes photo of home (Box 16)
    - Wetmore family (Box 16)
      (includes photos of home and Swains Lake, and tintype)
    - Whitmare, Henry A.-photo of home, Concord (Box 16)
    - Whittaker family-includes photo of home (Box 16)
    - Winchell, Carrie Simons (Box 16)
      (includes photos of camp and deer hunt, Upper Peninsula, 1930s)
    - Worth family (Box 16)
  - Motion pictures
    (All 8 mm. black & white, except where noted)
    - "No. 1 deer hunt", 1940-1943 (Box 17)
    - "No. 2 deer hunt", 1943 (Box 17)
    - Football and 1947 or 1948 deer hunt (Box 17)
    - Brigham's Buick Garage (Box 17)
    - "Pulaski 4-H Club", circa 1943 (Box 17)
    - Order of the Eastern Star (Box 17)
    - "4-H", color (Box 17)
    - "Deer hunt, parade", color (Box 17)
  - Negatives
    [Staff use only]
    - Negatives with prints in collection
      - Numbered negatives (Box 17)
        (1-7, 10-11, 13, 20-22, 24-26, 28, 32-33, 35, 39-40, 42-43, 48-57, 59-62, 64-67, 69, 74-75, 79, 81, 91-93, 95-96, 100-101, 107-109, 115-120, 125-131, 133, 140-141, 148, 151A, 151B, 152, 154-158, 160, 168-170, 172-178, 182-187)
      - Unnumbered negatives
        - Families (Box 17)
        - Subjects (Box 17)
    - Negatives without prints in collection
      - Families (Box 17)
        (includes Aldrich, French, Goodrich, Parmeter, Spratt)
      - Subjects (Box 17)
        (includes Concord schools and views, unidentified groups and individuals, baseball team, cornet band, businesses, grist mill, railroad depot)